

Awal Ariansyah Adaptive Software Engineer

+6283863434232

■ awalariansyah7@gmail.com

nowfluke.github.io

Cilacap, Indonesia

SUMMARY

Adaptive Software Engineer with 2+ years of experience across multiple platform and contemporary framework to deliver a performance, efficient and friendly execution of code through enjoyable debugging. Familiar with JS, PHP, MERN, Next, Astro, React Native, SQL, and Firebase.

What do I mean by Adaptive? I don't blame any environment, I adjust myself to suit it instead. Thank you HRD Manager for reading this. I hope you are doing well and keep going up. You deserved a happiness.

EXPERIENCE

Frontend Mobile Developer

10/2022 - 01/2023

PT. Anugerah Lestari Teknokreasi

Developing m-banking app for Android & iOS starts from UI/UX Designing until to code it in React Native

Backend Developer Internship

07/2022 - 08/2022

PT. Rejeki Berkah Nusantara

Internship to demonstrate migration from monolithic architecture into micro-services and building the frontend dashboard for business intelligent langitpay

Graphic Designer 08/2020 - 01/2021

Jenester

Designing UI/UX, logo and banner as a part time job based on client request

IT Support 11/2018 - 01/2019

SMK Komputama

Hardware and networking maintenance

EDUCATION

Informatics Engineering 08/2019 - 11/2023

STMIK Komputama Majenang - Bachelor's degree

- Dig deeper in computer, programming, software development, databases, and information system.
- Compete and won various software development competition

Network Engineering 2016 - 2019

SMK Komputama Majenang - High school

- · Learned basic computer, troubleshooting, algorithm, and networking
- · Compete and won various web design competition

CERTIFICATES

2nd PIKMI 2023 BSI Software Development Universitas Bina Sarana Informatika	06/2023 - Present
Finalist Top 10 Google Hackfest 2023 Google Developer Student Club Indonesia	03/2023 - Present
Participant inaRISK Creative Week UI/UX 2022 Badan Nasional Penanggulangan Bencana	10/2022 - Present
3rd Cyber 2022 Website Design Universitas Gorontalo	03/2022 - Present
1st Techcomfest 2022 Software Development Competition Politeknik Negeri Semarang	01/2022 - Present
Participant GEMASTIK XIV Software Development Kementrian Pendidikan dan Kebudayaan	10/2021 - Present
Finalist Top 10 CODE AMCC 2021 AMIKOM Yogyakarta	09/2021 - Present
Top 10 Finalist Techcomfest Network Competition 2019 Politeknik Negeri Semarang	02/2019 - Present
3rd LKS Web Design Competition MKKS SMK Kabupaten Cilacap	09/2018 - Present
Top 10 Finalist GEMASTE Web Design Competition 2018 Universitas Negeri Semarang	08/2018 - Present
2nd LKS Web Design Competition MKKS Kabupaten Cilacap	08/2017 - Present

SKILLS

Software Engineering	Advanced	Backend Server (PHP Native	Beginner
UI/UX Design & Prototyping (Figma)	Intermediate	& Laravel) Android & iOS (React Native)	Intermediate
Backend Server (Nodejs & Express)	Advanced	Automation (Bot & Scrapping)	Intermediate
Frontend Web (Reactjs & Solidjs)	Expert	Operating System (Linux & Windows)	Expert
SQL Databases (MySQL & PostgreSQL)	Intermediate	Misc (Team management, googling & problem solving)	Advanced
NoSQL Databases (Firebase & MongoDB)	Intermediate		

LANGUAGES

English	Fluent	Indonesian	Native
Lingilloni	TIGOTIC	maoneolan	TACTIVE